Good afternoon, Attorney!
Mm! Good afternoon.
Here.
Uh, you just woke up?
Oh!
No. I've been awake
for a while.
I already had our vinegar
delivered earlier.
Here, go buy yourself
some clothes.
I still have clothes
back there.
If you're going to inherit
Don Nato's 5-billion estate,
you should at least
look presentable.
F-Five billion?!
I'm inheriting five billion?!
You didn't know?
I knew the Roses were wealthy,
but I had no idea
they were that rich.
What did you think?
I thought...
it was just enough to buy
a small house for Ima and me.
The kind where we wouldn't
have to turn off the fridge
in the middle of the night...
just to save on electricity.
The kind where she wouldn't
have to walk all the way
to the market just
to save on transportation.
Just something like that.
Go buy what you need.
I don't want you
buying me anything--
[PING] It's a corporate card.
So technically, everything
you spend with it is your money.
Just take it.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Thank you.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh, are you surprised
she didn't know?
Everything about June
is surprising.
All she's ever wanted is for
her mom to live comfortably
and to help her family.
She is one of a kind.
[CHUCKLES]
In the end, it looks like
Don Nato was right
to have the two of you
get married.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]